Finding Aid for the Incoming Correspondence: Heinrich Meyer Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- R
  - Regnery, Henry, 25 July 1958 (Box 4)
  - Rehder, Helmut. (22), 2 May 1944 –27 May 1974, undated (Box 4)
  - Reichard, Iva R. Undated (Box 4)
  - Reichard, Joseph R. Undated (Box 4)
  - Reichard, Sue R. and Harry H. Undated (Box 4)
  - Reichart, W. A. (2), 8 July 1942 –1 November 1950 (Box 4)
  - Reicherts, ?, 19 December 1967 (Box 4)
  - Reiff, Bob. Christmas card, undated (Box 4)
  - Reimer, Lois, 17 April 1959 (Box 4)
  - Reimer, ? (2), 15 May 1936 –6 November 1966 (Box 4)
  - Reinsch, Don A. Undated (Box 4)
  - Reinsch, Frank H. (4), 2 January 1950 –4 August 1954 (Box 4)
  - Remak, Henry H. H. (3), 6 December 1958 –28 May 1971 (Box 4)
  - Renninger, Jesse B. (6), 6 July 1947 -November 1953, undated (Box 4)
  - Reske, Hermann, 4 April 1960 (Box 4)
  - Reston, James B, 20 September 1960 (Box 4)
  - Revard, James, 30 November 1967 (Box 4)
  - Rice, Brigitte. (2) Undated (Box 4)
  - Rice, Irene. Christmas, 1962 (Box 4)
  - Rice, Tommy. (15), 30 November 1939 –27 April 1961, undated (Box 4)
  - Richards, Clarinda. (18), 10 October 1944 –6 May 1945, undated (Box 4)
  - Richards, Don. (2), 2 February 1968 –27 May 1968 (Box 4)
  - Richter, Adolfo. (4), 17 September 1943 -27 June 1944, undated (Box 4)
  - Richter, Friedrich-Karl. (2), 27 November 1940 –29 September 1967 (Box 4)
  - Rickmann, Heinz, 11 October 1926 (Box 4)
  - Rickey, George. (10), 6 May 1947 –3 October 1954 (Box 4)
  - Rieduer, Tobias, 16 February 1945 (Box 4)
  - Riegel, S. M, 23 January 1942 (Box 4)
  - Riema, E. P, 17 January 1943 (Box 4)
  - Rieter, Fritz. (4), 28 October 1950 –1 December 1967 (Box 4)
  - Riez?, Werner, 31 August 1951 (Box 4)
  - Rigg, Alexander. (3), 3 June 1928 –30 September 1928, undated (Box 4)
  - Rigg, Robert. (2), 4 June 1928, undated (Box 4)
  - Riley, Joseph P, 2 June 1953 (Box 4)
  - Riley, Lenore Bunn, 26 May 1936 (Box 4)
  - Rinn, Hermann, 29 December 1949 (Box 4)
  - Rippley, La Vern J. Undated (Box 4)
  - Ritchee, C, 22 July 1970 (Box 4)
  - Rittenmeyer, F. (7), 1931 –23 December 1957 (Box 4)
  - Roarke, Ed, 20 January 1962 (Box 4)
  - Robbins, Marcus, 9 December 1949 (Box 4)
  - Robinson, Julia, 23 October 1934 (Box 4)
  - Rocke, Beth. (11), 1 August 1948 –18 November 1949, undated (Box 4)
  - Rodale, Jerry I. (34), 8 February 1945 –5 October 1966, undated (Box 4)
  - Rodale, Robert. (3), 19 February 1973 –22 March 1974 (Box 4)
  - Roeseler, R. D. (18), 18 February 1942 –27 May 1952 (Box 4)
  - Rohm, Walther, 28 March 1952 (Box 4)
  - Rohr, Hans. (8), 30 March 1960 –1 November 1972 (Box 4)
  - Rohrbach & Hill, 22 January 1971 (Box 4)
  - Rollins, Bernice, 26 January 1959 (Box 4)
  - Rollins, ?, 19 January ? (Box 4)
  - Roloff, Hans-Gert, 5 December 1969 (Box 4)
  - Rominger, Charles H, 2 February 1961 (Box 4)
  - Rondthaler, Theodore, 6 October 1945 (Box 4)
  - Roos, Jacques, 9 December 1952 (Box 4)
  - Root, T. Undated (Box 4)
  - Rose, Ernst. (4), 18 October 1949 –15 December 1966 (Box 4)
  - Rose, M. Undated (Box 4)
  - Rosenberg, Mary S. (2), 12 May 1950 –12 October 1966 (Box 4)
  - Rosenhaupt, Hans, 3 November 1965 (Box 4)
  - Rossmann, Doris. (5), 11 September 1929 –21 May 1959, undated (Box 4)
  - Rossmann, Fritz. (6), 31 December 1939-1961 (Box 4)
  - Rossmann, Ruth and Eric, 19 June 1952 (Box 4)
  - Rothe, Wolfgang, 26 April 1955 (Box 4)
  - Rotter, Federico. (10), 10 September 1943 –12 February 1954 (Box 4)
  - Rotter, Roswitha, 10 September 1947 (Box 4)
  - Rowell, Donna, 15 August 1952 (Box 4)
  - Rowley, Marjorie M, 31 May 1971 (Box 4)
  - Rouall, R. R, 20 May 1942 (Box 4)
  - Ruck, Johanna. (2), 6 December 1952 –11 December 1952 (Box 4)
  - Rücker, Elisabeth, 7 November 1966 (Box 4)
  - Rudkin, Margaret, 11 April 1950 (Box 4)
  - Rueger, Homer, 8 December 1958 (Box 4)
  - Rugg, ?, 16 October 1940 (Box 4)
  - Rumpf, Josefine, 30 September 1965 (Box 4)
  - Russi, Fred. (2), 27 September 1939 –9 October 1939 (Box 4)
  - Rust-Oppenheim, August, 29 December 1942 (Box 4)
  - Rutledge, John. (2), 4 August 1972 –7 December 1972 (Box 4)
  - Rutledge, Joyce. (3), 7 November 1972 –7 January 1974 (Box 4)
  - Ryberg, Josef E, 14 June 1952 (Box 4)
  - Ryser, Doris, 7 December 1966 (Box 4)
- S
  - Saintsbury, Dorothy. (2), 26 February 1951 –7 February 1956 (Box 4)
  - Salfinger, Th. (8), 12 January 1952 –8 August 1972 (Box 4)
  - Salinger, Herman, 27 May 1955 (Box 4)
  - Salloch, William. (3), 12 March 1953 –9 May 1974 (Box 4)
  - Sameth, Sigmund. (4), 22 September 1944 –27 March 1945 (Box 4)
  - Sammons, Wheeler. (2), 8 May 1950 –15 May 1950 (Box 4)
  - Sanchez, S. Undated (Box 4)
  - Sandoe, James. (3), 4 November 1943 –14 November 1943 (Box 4)
  - Sapp, Kenneth F, 5 February 1970 (Box 4)
  - Sarratt, Madison. Christmas card, undated (Box 4)
  - Sarton, ?, 5 November 1952 (Box 4)
  - Sass, Allan. (2), 4 May 1972 –9 May 1972 (Box 4)
  - Sauer, H. (3), 6 August 1949 –3 January 1951 (Box 4)
  - Saurjer, Nancy. Undated (Box 4)
  - Savage, D. A. (2), 20 July 1945 –30 July 1945 (Box 4)
  - Scardanelli, ?, 24 February 1968 (Box 4)
  - Scardigli, Piergiuseppe, September 1967 (Box 4)
  - Schatzki, Walter, 2 March 1955 (Box 4)
  - Sceurman, R. E. (2), 7 October 1952 –31 December 1952 (Box 4)
  - Schaedel, Mrs. J. (7) [to Mrs. Meyer], 4 February 1958 –16 June 1958 (Box 4)
  - Schaefer, Guillermo, 7 August 1946 (Box 4)
  - Schaefer, Wilhelm. (2), 20 December 1943 -14 May 1945 (Box 4)
  - Schaffer, Aaron. (2), 22 January 1941 –10 February 1941 (Box 4)
  - Schatzberg, Walter. (7), 18 November 1963 –12 February 1974 (Box 4)
  - Schaūur, Konrad. (7), 8 June 1958 –19 December 1971, undated (Box 4)
  - Scheck, Helmut. (3), 29 October 1950 –16 December 1950 (Box 4)
  - Scheffer, Peter, 29 November 1971 (Box 4)
  - Schefter, Lore. (4), 27 March 1954 –16 December 1954 (Box 4)
  - Scheider, Rose M, 29 September 1965 (Box 4)
  - Schellenberg, Ernst. (20), 17 August 1942 –6 December 1971 (Box 4)
  - Schenesmayer, Liesel, 13 November 1949 (Box 4)
  - Scherman, Harry, 18 February 1960 (Box 4)
  - Scheyer, Ernst. (2), 24 October 1949 –22 December 1949 (Box 4)
  - Schick, Edgar B. (4), 10 November 1955 –29 February 1960, undated (Box 4)
  - Schillemeit, Jost, 22 January 1974 (Box 4)
  - Schindler, Wilhelm Ludwig, 5 November 1972 (Box 4)
  - Schircks, Eberhard, 13 June 1949 (Box 4)
  - Schirokauer, Arno. (12), 5 July 1942 -4 March 1953, undated (Box 4)
  - Schleidt, Margret, 21 December 1966 (Box 4)
  - Schleinmetz, ?, 16 October 1949 (Box 4)
  - Schlenker, Luther F, 1 June 1960 (Box 4)
  - Schloffer, Eva-Verena, 16 October 1945 (Box 4)
  - Scholz, Gerhard, 24 September 1951 (Box 4)
  - Schmalbeck, Gugrun, 13 October 1971 (Box 4)
  - Schmetz, Stefan, 11 April 1965 (Box 4)
  - Schmidt, Josef, 18 January 1971 (Box 4)
  - Schmitt, Elisabth D, 17 April 1950 (Box 4)
  - Schmitt, E. Otto. Undated (Box 4)
  - Schmitz, Matthais, 6 March 1947 (Box 4)
  - Schnappauf, Erich. (4), 18 October 1964 –18 February 1967, undated (Box 4)
  - Schnard, G. C. L, 28 January 1950 (Box 4)
  - Schneider, Alfred, 27 July 1964 (Box 4)
  - Schneider, K. L. (4), 6 April 1961 –17 October 1962 (Box 4)
  - Schneider, Sonia and Arthur. Christmas card, undated (Box 4)
  - Schocken, Salman. (3), 2 February 1949 –28 February 1949 (Box 4)
  - Scholte, J. H. (2), 2 November 1925 –30 August 1928 (Box 4)
  - Schöndorf, Anton (2), 15 July 1963 –30 January 1973 (Box 4)
  - Schöne, Wolfgang. (2), 25 August 1961 –1967 (Box 4)
  - Schrader, Edda. (2), 8 January 1967 –17 January 1967 (Box 4)
  - Schrecker, Paul, 29 April 1948 (Box 4)
  - Schreiber, Carl F. (7), 23 January 1948 –13 September 1953 (Box 4)
  - Schremmer, E, 7 July 1950 –31 August 1950 (Box 4)
  - Schroeder, Paul. (5), 20 April 1942 –27 November 1943 (Box 4)
  - Schuchard, Gottfried C. L, 6 July 1950 (Box 4)
  - Schulz, Otrud, 21 September 1944 (Box 4)
  - Schultz, H. Stefan. (3), 11 January 1950 –5 December 1966 (Box 4)
  - Schultz, J. H, 19 May 1964 (Box 4)
  - Schuman, Henry. (4), 30 April 1949 –23 January 1952 (Box 4)
  - Schumann, Detlev. (15), 20 January 1946 –2 April 1967 (Box 4)
  - Schumann and Corbet, 8 August 1952 (Box 4)
  - Schurr, Dora and Josef, 21 December 1959 (Box 4)
  - Schurr, Hans. (7), 21 February 1955 –16 February 1965 (Box 4)
  - Schwander, P. W, 16 October 1938 (Box 4)
  - Schwartz, H. K. Undated (Box 4)
  - Schwarz, Egon. (10), 24 March 1960 –16 December 1966, undated (Box 4)
  - Schwarze, E, 21 October 1926 (Box 4)
  - Schwender, Fred O. Undated (Box 4)
  - Schwiening, ?, 10 April 1953 (Box 4)
  - Schwietering, J. (3), 21 May 1954 –14 May 1960, undated (Box 4)
  - Scott, Charles, 27 November 1966 (Box 4)
  - Scott, Harry A, 15 April 1935 (Box 4)
  - Scott, L. Lon. (3), 17 August 1951, undated (Box 4)
  - Seegers, J. C. (11), 31 December 1952 –8 July 1960 (Box 4)
  - Seering, Christopher, 30 September 1954 (Box 4)
  - Segessman, Harry. (2), 15 April 1963 –26 April 1963 (Box 4)
  - Sehlmeyer, A, 9 September 1946 (Box 4)
  - Seibold, C. E, 1 November 1949 (Box 4)
  - Seidlin, Oskar. (3), 9 February 1949 –2 February 1968, undated (Box 4)
  - Seiferth, Wolfgang. (3), 28 October 1949 –10 December 1949 (Box 4)
  - Seki, Yayoi. (3), 29 April 1951 –5 June 1951 (Box 4)
  - Sell, F. C, 27 July 1948 (Box 4)
  - Selph, Betty, 1 March 1972 (Box 4)
  - Sel?, 5 December 1949 (Box 4)
  - Sengle, Friedrich. (5), 5 June 1954 –11 November 1960 (Box 4)
  - Senn, Alfred. (7), 5 May 1953 –17 January 1974, undated (Box 4)
  - Senour, Helen, 6 February 1940 (Box 4)
  - Sewell, Elisabeth. (10), 5 December 1947 –18 December 1962, undated (Box 4)
  - Seyfarth, Erich. (2), 6 August 1934 –28 January 1935 (Box 4)
  - Shankweiler, ? Undated (Box 4)
  - Sharrar, Lee M. Undated (Box 4)
  - Shaw, Gertrude. (2), 23 October 1943 –29 October 1943 (Box 4)
  - Shaw, Theodore L. (2), 2 February 1960 –16 March 1960 (Box 4)
  - Shelton, Roy. (2), 9 October 1967 –15 December 1971 (Box 4)
  - Shepherd, Patricia Drake, 27 January 1954 (Box 4)
  - Sherman, Bill. Christmas card, undated (Box 4)
  - Sherr, Paul. (18), 8 April 1944 –12 December 1972, undated (Box 4)
  - Sherwood, Ethel, 23 October 1944 (Box 4)
  - Shiles, Jonah W. D, 9 November 1951 (Box 4)
  - Shoemaker, Whitney, 15 January 1968 (Box 4)
  - Shouvlin, R. J, 6 November 1946 (Box 4)
  - Siber, Helmut O. C. (8), 17 April 1945 –6 June 1947 (Box 4)
  - Sibert, J-L, 31 July 1952 (Box 4)
  - Siegfried, Marylou. (4, 30 October 1942 –8 December 1942, undated (Box 4)
  - Silverman, S, 4 March 1950 (Box 4)
  - Silz, Walter. (2), 16 May 1954, undated (Box 4)
  - Simon, Richard L, 1 October 1946 (Box 4)
  - Simon, Werner. (4), 12 June 1964 –1973 (Box 4)
  - Sims, Norman. Undated (Box 4)
  - Skweir, Michael J, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Slate, George L. (2), 10 October 1945 –7 January 1947 (Box 4)
  - Smelter, Roy E, 28 May 1949 (Box 4)
  - Smith, E. Burrows, 13 December 1965 (Box 4)
  - Smith, Howard A. Undated (Box 4)
  - Smith, J. Edward, 2 March 1959 (Box 4)
  - Smith, Roger W. (7), 23 December 1945 –28 July 1946, undated (Box 4)
  - Smith, Wilbur J. (3), 6 February 1953 –12 October 1953, undated (Box 4)
  - Smoyer, F, 17 March 1956 (Box 4)
  - Smyth, Mac C, 5 March 1943 (Box 4)
  - Snyder, Gloria P. (3), 22 February 1953 –30 April 1953 (Box 4)
  - Snyder, Kathleen M, 26 March 1946 (Box 4)
  - Sohdell, Bill. Christmas card, undated (Box 4)
  - Soifer, Margaret K, 21 November 1945 (Box 4)
  - Solbrig, Ingeborg. (3), 20 September 1970 –17 November 1971, undated (Box 4)
  - Sotheran, Henry Ltd. (5), 20 December 1950 –20 September 1966 (Box 4)
  - Souter, ?, 1929 (Box 4)
  - Spahr, Blake Lee. (2), 16 August 1967 –8 November 1967 (Box 4)
  - Spain, William. Undated (Box 4)
  - Sparks, T. Ashley, 23 June 1948 (Box 4)
  - Spaulding, John A. (15), 26 June 1949 –20 October 1954 (Box 4)
  - Speiden, Evelyn. (5), 10 October 1945 –30 March 1946, undated (Box 4)
  - Speiser, Andreas. (2), 13 February 1954 –23 December 1963 (Box 4)
  - Spinner, Gerhard, 10 January 1974 (Box 4)
  - Sprenger, Otto. (9), 13 July 1936 –4 January 1955 (Box 4)
  - Springeli, Albin. (17), 1 December 1966 –30 July 1973 (Box 4)
  - Sprofkin, Bertram E, 9 August 1974 (Box 4)
  - Spycher, Peter. (37), 2 June 1952 –21 January 1974, undated (Box 4)
  - Staber, Dorothy, 6 September 1944 (Box 4)
  - Stahl, Heide. (3), 5 April 1966 -24 April 1966, undated (Box 4)
  - Stahley, Esther R. (2) Undated (Box 4)
  - Stahley, Wilmer F. (4), 9 February 1961 –21 December 1964 (Box 4)
  - Staiger, Emil, 10 December 1967 (Box 4)
  - Stammer’s Bookstore. Undated (Box 4)
  - Stanfield, J Fisher, 5 September 1945 (Box 4)
  - Stanley, Teeto and George. Undated (Box 4)
  - Stapf, Paul. (17), 28 January 1967 –6 March 1973, undated (Box 4)
  - Starck, Taylor. (7), 2 May 1940 –15 January 1949 (Box 4)
  - Stauffacher, Werner, 20 November 1973 (Box 4)
  - Stechert, G. E. & Co. (2), 29 March 1937 –20 November 1943 (Box 4)
  - Stechert and Hafner Inc. (7), 1 August 1950 –3 October 1967 (Box 4)
  - Steegemann, ?, 1 December 1955 (Box 4)
  - Steel, Eric M, 16 November 1965 (Box 4)
  - Steer Jr., A. G, 29 November 1971 (Box 4)
  - Stegemeier, Henri, 13 February 1950 (Box 4)
  - Steichmann, H, 21 February 1941 (Box 4)
  - Steiger, Hugo. (2), 18 June 1936 –30 December 1937 (Box 4)
  - Stein, Jack M. (4), 17 November 1953 –9 March 1967, undated (Box 4)
  - Steiner, Herbert. (2), 26 February 1942 -3 November 1949 (Box 4)
  - Steinhauer, Harry. (3), 3 May 1954 –5 December 1958 (Box 4)
  - Stenderhoff, Heinrich, 3 September 1959 (Box 4)
  - Stengel, Therese. (2) Undated (Box 4)
  - Stephens, Pauline Frances. (3), 10 January 1959 –27 January 1959 (Box 4)
  - Stern, Guy. (4), 22 November 1971 –2 May 1973 (Box 4)
  - Stern, Hans, 16 October 1971 (Box 4)
  - Sternfeld, Frederick W. (7), 24 August 1952 –4 February 1955 (Box 4)
  - Stevens, Edward B. (4), 30 June 1952 –21 August 1955, undated (Box 4)
  - Stevens, Henry H, 6 January 1953 (Box 4)
  - Stevens, J, 26 September 1955 (Box 4)
  - Stevens, Lera, 19 May 1964 (Box 4)
  - Stine, Russell W. (3), 28 November 1949 –1958 (Box 4)
  - Stolt, Birgit. (4), 12 January 1971 –14 May 1972 (Box 4)
  - Stout, A. B. (3), 28 May 1946 –18 February 1947 (Box 4)
  - Stow, Lloyd. Undated (Box 4)
  - Strauss, E, 12 January 1950 (Box 4)
  - Strauss, Robert S, 21 June 1973 (Box 4)
  - Streisand, Hugo. (2), 31 May 1963, undated (Box 4)
  - Strieber, Kay. (2), 10 December 1967, undated (Box 4)
  - Strietelmeier, John, 23 December 1958 (Box 4)
  - Stronks, William. (3), 19 April 1968 –9 July 1968, undated (Box 4)
  - Strothman, F. W. (2), 1 December 1949 –5 October 1950 (Box 4)
  - Struck, Hartwig. (2), 15 February 1960 –12 April 1961 (Box 4)
  - Stubbe, Gerhard. (3), 23 January 1948 –31 April 1950 (Box 4)
  - Stuckenbrock, Karl-Heinz, 30 July 1974 (Box 4)
  - Stuempel, Helmut, 4 February 1970 (Box 4)
  - Stuhlee, G. (2), 7 February 1942 –22 September 1950 (Box 4)
  - Stuhlsatz, Michel J and Vanita. (2), 5 January 1946, undated (Box 4)
  - Stumpp and Walter Co, 1 November 1945 (Box 4)
  - Suchier, R, 30 May 1968 (Box 4)
  - Suckling, George L. (3), 17 December 1951 –23 March 1959 (Box 4)
  - Sudermann, Jacob. (3), 17 June 1969 –2 July 1970 (Box 4)
  - Sudhof, S, 19 December 1973 (Box 4)
  - Sullivan, Patricia, 25 August 1955 (Box 4)
  - Summerlin, George T, 14 October 1940 (Box 4)
  - Sundermeyer, William K. (6), 30 October 1949 –18 December 1950, undated (Box 4)
  - Sutherland, D, 7 October 1966 (Box 4)
  - Sutherland, Jane, 12 October 1966 (Box 4)
  - Suzuki, Hiromasa. (16), 29 June 1951 –1 November 1962, undated (Box 4)
  - Svendsen, Kester. (2), 20 November 1959 –30 November 1959 (Box 4)
  - Sveterman, ? Christmas card, undated (Box 4)
  - Swain, J. (2) Undated (Box 4)
  - Swartley, John C, 22 September 1946 (Box 4)
  - Swartz, Ralph C, 17 June 1955 (Box 4)
  - Swint, Betty. (2), 21 August 1964 –28 April 1965 (Box 4)
- T
  - Tarbruegge, Marilyn, 9 January 1968 (Box 4)
  - Tart Jr., Stephen M, 11 August 1964 (Box 4)
  - Tasso, Annabelle, 6 June 1968 (Box 4)
  - Tatum Jr., Liston, 22 February 1943 (Box 4)
  - Taub, Max, 25 January 1941 (Box 4)
  - Tax, Piet. (3), 18 October 1967 –8 June 1968 (Box 4)
  - Taylor, Archer. (25), 7 January 1942 –18 October 1962, undated (Box 4)
  - Taylor, Coley. (2), 13 January 1947, undated (Box 4)
  - Taylor, Ronald. (4), 30 November 1967 –22 February 1973, undated (Box 4)
  - Taylor, Sally G, 3 April 1948 (Box 4)
  - Theda, Katharine. (2), 5 April 1948 –12 April 1948 (Box 4)
  - Thelen, Albert Vigoleis, 14 April 1970 (Box 4)
  - Thewman, George. (7), 12 October 1966 –24 July 1974 (Box 4)
  - Theyerl, Maria, 7 October 1949 (Box 4)
  - Thiel, M. (3), 23 March 1960 –20 April 1965 (Box 4)
  - Thom, Huntington, 12 January 1939 (Box 4)
  - Thomas, Albert, 4 February 1941 (Box 4)
  - Thomas, J. D. (5), 17 November 1953 –30 December 1973 (Box 4)
  - Thomas, L. H. C, 24 April 1967 (Box 4)
  - Thomas, Norman, 17 December 1961 (Box 4)
  - Thomas, W. C, 4 March 1946 (Box 4)
  - Thompson, James Westfall, 1 May 1937 (Box 4)
  - Thompson, Robert J. Undated (Box 4)
  - Thorndike, Lynn, 20 November 1946 (Box 4)
  - Thurnner, Eugen, 24 April 1961 (Box 4)
  - Tilhof?, T, 27 July 1934 (Box 4)
  - Tilsher, Warner G. (11), 26 October 1946 –27 July 1948 (Box 4)
  - Tipton, Georgia and John. (2) Christmas cards, undated (Box 4)
  - Tipton, Sunny and Bob, January 1947 (Box 4)
  - Todd, William B, 9 July 1963 (Box 4)
  - Toennies, Gernt and Dita. (3), 5 December 1950, undated (Box 4)
  - Tolstoi, Anne. Undated (Box 4)
  - Tomforde, A. M. (3), 5 November 1942 –23 August 1947 (Box 4)
  - Toothman, H. F, 17 July 1951 (Box 4)
  - Toppman, Lea T, 20 October 1952 (Box 4)
  - Tourtellot, Francis. (10), June 1949 –29 January 1952 (Box 4)
  - Townsend, Stanley R. (2), 11 January 1954 –24 May 1954 (Box 4)
  - Tratho, Meredith. Undated (Box 4)
  - Treichler, Bette. Christmas card, undated [see also Bette Cioffi] (Box 4)
  - Treichler, Chas, 31 October 1953 (Box 4)
  - Trevelyan, G. M, 19 February 1952 (Box 4)
  - Triplett, William C, 11 March 1942 (Box 4)
  - Trog, Hermann, 1 April 1968 (Box 4)
  - Trunz, Erich. (4), 29 September 1950 –7 October 1971 (Box 4)
  - Tubach, Frederic C, 18 July 1960 (Box 4)
  - Tüffenhammer, Margarete. (15), 23 August 1932 –20 December 1973, undated (Box 4)
  - Tully, Grace G, 28 October 1941 (Box 4)
  - Tümmler, H, 20 December 1962 (Box 4)
  - Türk, Barbara, 12 July 1961 (Box 4)
  - Turner, John B. (7), 16 October 1944 –3 November 1946, undated (Box 4)
  - Tyson, Levering. (6), 27 March 1950 –28 October 1954 (Box 4)
- U
  - Ulmer, Bernard. (4), 11 February 1950 –7 January 1970 (Box 4)
  - Ulmer, Eugen, 24 March 1949 (Box 4)
  - Ungar, Frederick. (2), 20 December 1954 –16 February 1965 (Box 4)
  - Unseld, Siegfried, 1 November 1972 (Box 4)
  - Urzidil, Johannes, 12 September 1965 (Box 4)
- V
  - Vail, Curtis C. D. (6), 18 January 1952 –25 October 1954 (Box 4)
  - Van Sant, John T, 11 September 1959 (Box 4)
  - Van Vechten, Carl. (2), 2 February 1955 –14 February 1955 (Box 4)
  - Vasady, Bela. (2), 14 March 1950, undated (Box 4)
  - Veneter, ?, 30 December 1934 (Box 4)
  - Verdoorn, Frans. (4), 22 November 1946 –24 February 1947 (Box 4)
  - Verry, L. I. (2), 29 April 1942 –30 June 1942 (Box 4)
  - Vilho, ? Undated (Box 4)
  - Vines, Robert A, 29 March 1946 (Box 4)
  - Vlach, Robert. (22), 31 August 1961 –8 December 1965 (Box 4)
  - Vollmer, Clement. (6), 22 March 1955 –23 April 1955 (Box 4)
- W
  - Waas, Glenn, 5 November 1965 (Box 4)
  - Wachinger, Burghard. (3), 25 January 1960 –29 April 1960 (Box 4)
  - Wachs, Morris, 2 March 1967 (Box 4)
  - Wade, Ira O. (10), 6 May 1954 –13 March 1956 (Box 4)
  - Wagemann, Henry T. Undated (Box 4)
  - Wagner, Constance. (2), 8 September 1967 –6 January 1970 (Box 4)
  - Waldburger, Paul, 11 September 1973 (Box 4)
  - Waldinger, Ernst. (2), 7 May 1961, undated (Box 4)
  - Walle, Mary R, 24 August 1946 (Box 4)
  - Walleristen?, H, 15 April 1971 (Box 4)
  - Wallrich, Larry and Ruby. Christmas card, 1963 (Box 4)
  - Walsh, Donald D. (2), 24 October 1963 –11 December 1963 (Box 4)
  - Walters, Basil L. (2), 30 October 1946 –6 November 1946 (Box 4)
  - Wandruszka, Mario, 4 January 1970 (Box 4)
  - Ward, Robert. (7), 27 June 1967 –1 November 1973 (Box 4)
  - Ware, Romaine. (2), 21 July 1947 –9 August 1947 (Box 4)
  - Warner, S. R, 3 October 1944 (Box 4)
  - Wask, George. Christmas card, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Wassermann, Earl R. (2), 1 February 1973 –6 February 1973 (Box 4)
  - Wassermann, F. M. (7), 24 September 1949 –10 April 1970 (Box 4)
  - Waterhouse, Margaret. (5), 26 February 1949 –12 September 1948 (Box 4)
  - Watson, ? Christmas card, undated (Box 4)
  - Watts, Evelyn. (2), 3 November 1944 –8 January 1945 (Box 4)
  - Watts, W. H, 6 June 1972 (Box 4)
  - Weaver, Henry, 6 December 1943 (Box 4)
  - Weaver, Polly. (2), 14 October 1948 –14 December 1948 (Box 4)
  - Webb, R. O. (6), 9 March 1943 –3 July 1944 (Box 4)
  - Weber, Edgar A, 31 May 1949 (Box 4)
  - Weber, Werner, 16 June 1970 (Box 4)
  - Webster, T. D. (2), 8 May 1953 –14 May 1953 (Box 4)
  - Wegner, Christian. (10), 27 July 1950 –29 October 1963 (Box 4)
  - Wegner, Matthais. (2), 29 September 1967 –26 October 1967 (Box 4)
  - Wegner, Nicholas, 29 March 1970 (Box 4)
  - Wehnert, E, 28 March 1931? (Box 4)
  - Wehrli, Max, 8 April 1971 (Box 4)
  - Weikert, F, 11 July 1917 (Box 4)
  - Weigand, Hermann J. (82), 19 January 1941 –17 September 1968, undated (Box 4)
  - Weigand, Paul, 2 July 1954 (Box 4)
  - Weiner, ? (2), 14 May 1952 –23 June 1952 (Box 4)
  - Weinert, John (2), 6 May 1953 –27 April 1969 (Box 4)
  - Weinstock, Herbert, 16 January 1947 (Box 4)
  - Weischedel, Hanna. (2), 8 July 1969, undated (Box 4)
  - Weise, Julius. (3), 14 February 1962 –24 September 1965 (Box 4)
  - Weiss, Harold S, 9 May 1952 (Box 4)
  - Weiss, K. (2), 28 December 1943 –4 March 1944 (Box 4)
  - Weisstein, Ulrich. (3), 1 January 1959 –23 January 1974 (Box 4)
  - Welch, Helen W. (4), 14 January 1953 –25 October 1955 (Box 4)
  - Wentz, Alfred W, 20 October 1953 (Box 4)
  - Wenzel, H. (8), 22 September 1970 –27 September 1972 (Box 4)
  - Weth, Rose A. (10), 11 June 1972 –December 1973, undated (Box 4)
  - Whalen, Wm. A, 29 October 1935 (Box 4)
  - Wheeler, Burton K. (2), 11 July 1941, undated (Box 4)
  - Wheeler, Harvey, 3 January 1972 (Box 4)
  - Wheeler, Stanley G. (2), 14 March 1952 –18 June 1959 (Box 4)
  - Whitaker, Paul K. (5), 12 November 1959 –26 October 1970 (Box 4)
  - White, Harold, 14 May 1933 (Box 4)
  - White, Herbert Clarence, 20 October 1946 (Box 4)
  - White, Vivian. (2), 1 November 1932 –13 May 1933 (Box 4)
  - Whitman, Alden, 10 July 1967 (Box 4)
  - Whitesell, Frederick R. (6), 21 October 1970 –10 November 1973, undated (Box 4)
  - Whyte, John, 21 November 1949 (Box 4)
  - Wickenden, Leonard, 27 July 1947 (Box 4)
  - Wieck, Fred. (4), 13 January 1948 –11 June 1948 (Box 4)
  - Wiegel, Mrs. Undated (Box 4)
  - Wiemer, ?, 5 June 1952 (Box 4)
  - Wiener, Norbert, 8 November 1949 (Box 4)
  - Wilber, Allen. (2), 13 January 1953 –26 January 1953 (Box 4)
  - Wilbur, Lorraine. (3), 8 June 1962 –29 October 1962 (Box 4)
  - Wilhelm, Friedrik. (5), 17 March 1928 –18 September 1933, undated (Box 4)
  - Wijngaards, N. C. H. (4), 10 October 1970 –6 July1972 (Box 4)
  - Wilkerson, M. M, 10 July 1950 –18 July 1950 (Box 4)
  - Wilkie, Richard F. (2), 6 October 1943 –1 November 1943 (Box 4)
  - Wilkinson, Gary. (3), 12 September 1949 –12 November 1954 (Box 4)
  - Willcox, O. W, 6 November 1944 (Box 4)
  - Williams, Albert, 8 September 1962 (Box 4)
  - Williams, Cora. [To Mrs. Dinsmoor] Undated (Box 4)
  - Williams, Curtis, 30 December 1954 (Box 4)
  - Williams, Everett. (2), 28 May 1947 –27 June 1947 (Box 4)
  - Williams. George. (46), 23 December 1942 –5 October 1973 (Box 4)
  - Williams, Jeff. (20), 21 April 1971 –25 November 1973, undated (Box 4)
  - Williams, Margaret, 25 April 1960 (Box 4)
  - Williams, Mark, 29 June 1970 (Box 4)